哈拉上路
欢迎光临艾菲嘉大学
我今天带大家好好参观一下
尽量带你们看看你们需要看的
这是学校的主校园
你们将会适应这个地方
这是同学们聚会的地方
大家过来，靠近点儿
以前有人掉过队，知道吗？
落在后面被车撞了
这不太好，这是…
这是乔瑟夫.H.尼尔逊图书馆
建于…十七世纪
十七世纪？这儿写着1951
那是地址，小聪明
那是心理系
你们都要自愿参加尖端的实验
很好玩的
到时记住穿宽松衫，别带金属
做好接受多次强电击的准备
他们现在正在注视我们
那边儿是英文系
你们大部分都说英语
我就不介绍了
你在这儿多久了？
八年
你看起来知道得不多
这是最差的一次参观
这是最差的学校
这里有过瘾的事儿吗？
有，当然有
这是世界上最有趣的大学
这是因为他没见过世面
笑吧，笑个够好了
但实情是，最伟大的故事
就发生在这儿
知道吗？
是我认识的一个人
乔希帕克
以及他的女友v芬妮的故事
这是最有趣的旅途之一
乔希和v芬妮青梅竹马
从小就在一起
他们总是一起做事
v芬妮十岁那年割扁桃体
乔希在医院陪了她三天
他们是最要好的朋友
'They were best friends.
纯真的友情逐渐开花结果…
'What started out as friendship...
演变成接吻与爱抚
'blossomed into some serious French
kissing and lots of heavy petting.
他们常常在一起
以致他俩的狗也开始约会了
'They spent so much time together
that even their dogs started dating.
他们似乎.注定一生都要在一起
'They seemed destined
to be together forever.
但高中毕业后
他们面临着最严峻的考验
'But after high school, they faced
the most challenging challenge ever -
海角天涯的关系
'a long-distance relationship.
乔希进了美妙的艾菲嘉大学
'See, while Josh was enrolled here at
the wonderful University of Ithaca,
v芬妮去了德州
奥斯丁兽医学院
'Tiffany went off to
veterinary school in Austin, Texas.
但他们盟誓要彼此忠诚
'But they made a pact,
a promise to stay true to each other,
每日通电，不见异思迁
'to talk every day and maintain
an exclusive relationship.'
他俩都没想到这实在是不容易
That turned out to be more difficult
than either of them ever imagined.
v芬妮！嗨，宝贝儿
Tiffany! Hey, baby.
啊，上帝，你昨晚棒极了
Oh, my God.
You were amazing last night.
你我从来也没这样过
你别逗了
- I never ever came like that before.
- Come on!
真的，我今早要吃两粒避孕片
Seriously! I had to take
two birth control pills today.
今晚还来帮我复习功课吗？
You wanna help me study
again tonight?
不等今晚了，现在就来
Forget tonight. Come over now.
我们不去上课了
Let's blow this class off.
v芬妮和卡拉不在，请留言
'Tiffany and Carla can't come to the
phone but please leave a message.'
嗨，v，又是我…
- (Beep )
- Hey, Tif, it's me...again.
不知道你在哪儿
仍在设法与你联系
Just wonderin' where you are.
Still trying to get hold of you.
一切都好，我再与你联系
Everything's cool, though.
I'll catch you later.
打电话给我，好吗？再见
Call me back, OK? OK. Bye.
录像带寄出前我想加点儿东西
I just wanted to add something
before I sent this video.
我好几天没跟你说话了…
I haven't talked to you
in a few days and...
我想你不喜欢我了，开玩笑
I'm thinking you don't like me...
I'm kidding.
嗨，伙计们
Hey, guys.
我开始有点担心
有空给我打电话
But I am getting a little worried so
gimme a call when you get a chance.
巴里问你好
Barry says hi.
一有空马上来电话，我想你
So gimme a call
as soon as you can. I miss you.
打电话来，好吗？再见
- Call me, OK? Bye.
- (Laughing)
你们在干什么？
没干什么，你呢？
- What's up, guys?
- Not much. You?
我在完成给v芬妮的录像带
I was just finishing my tape to Tif.
米切，你在干什么？饿吗？
(Barry ) Mitch, what are you doing?
Are you hungry? Huh?
你要喂它吗？
不，我在检查温度
- You gonna feed him?
- No, I'm checking the temperature.
米切需要华氏85度的恒温
Mitch needs an evenly distributed
85 degrees to survive.
我放进一只老鼠好不好？
Can I drop a mouse in?
米切每周只进一餐，在星期六
Mitch only eats once a week,
on Saturdays.
也许我们应该把老鼠剁开
Maybe we could cut a mouse in half,
现在喂一半，星期六喂一半
and we could feed him half now
and the other half on Saturday.
不，你不是有课吗？
I don't think so.
I thought you had class now?
几点了？啊，他妈的！
What time is it? Oh, shit!
帮我个忙－
这个倒好后替我寄了，好吗？
Do me a favour -
when this is rewound, mail it for me?
没问题，放那儿吧
谢谢
- No problem. Leave it there.
- Thanks, man.
回头见
再见
- See you guys later.
- Bye.
我们现在可以喂它吗？
Can we please feed him now?
不行，它吃得太多会死的
No. If you overfeed him he could die.
怎么啦？那也值得
So? It'll be worth it.
乔希，嗨
贝思，嗨
- Josh, hey.
- Beth, hey.
你怎么样？
还好
- What's goin' on?
- Not much.
你去哪儿了
没去哪儿
- Where have you been?
- Nowhere.
读书，我开始怀疑大学教育了
Studying. I'm starting
to question this college thing.
要读那么多的书
There's so much reading.
你对
你是啊
- Right. (Chuckles )
- Yeah.
你今晚去EL的晚会吗？
去
- You going to EL's tonight?
- Yeah.
我得走了，我的课已经开始了
(Josh) I gotta run,
class has started.
晚上见
对不起
- I'll see you tonight.
- Yeah. Sorry.
你看上他了，是不是？
So, you have a thing
for that guy now, is that it?
不关你的事，雅各布
我可以看出来
- It's not your business, Jacob.
- I can tell.
我不想与你谈这个
谈什么？
- I'm not having this conversation.
- What conversation?
你别再这样了，我们不是一对
You need to stop this.
We're not a couple.
从来就不是，将来也不会是
We've never been a couple,
and never will.
这星期我想让你们想想
(Professor) This week
I'd like you to think about
柏拉图的中期对话文章
Plato's Dialogues
of the middle years.
“共和国”
“p尔多”，   “论文集”
"The Republic", "Phaedo",
"Symposium".
下周的期中考试要考这些
Now, this will all be
on next week's mid-term,
我建议你们好好复习一下儿
so I suggest you read up on it.
雅各布，你有什么要补充吗？
Ah, Jacob,
do you have anything to add?
提醒一下儿
Just a reminder.
期中考试包括所有的讲课内容
The mid-term will cover
all of the in-class lectures
还有所有要求阅读的材料
as well as
all of the assigned readings.
考试形式是写论文
大家带正规纸来
It will be entirely essay form,
so bring legal pads.
最好是黄色的，对眼睛有好处
I prefer yellow.
It's easier on the eyes.
好，好，谢谢你，雅各布
OK. OK? Yeah. Thank you, Jacob.
那…下星期考场见
And...see you all next week
for the mid-term.
乔希
嗯？
- Josh.
- Yes?
我看见你搞上贝思了，这不好
I saw you hitting on Beth.
NOT a good idea.
她说过
什么？
- She's spoken for.
- What?
她会回来找我，她们都是这样
She'll come back to me.
They always do.
啊…帕克先生
So... Mr Parker.
你打算好好准备考试吗？
Do you intend
to be ready for this exam?
是，先生
那你好好准备
- Yes, sir.
- Well, you better be ready.
因为昨晚我查看了成绩单
Because I was
looking over the books last night
你要拿到B才能通过
and you need a B on this test
just to pass this class.
实际上我又查了一遍，教授
Actually,
I double-checked that, Professor.
他得拿B+，不能讲情
He needs a B+.
We can't bend on this.
我知道了
I got it.
你抄别人的好了
你不行，因为是论文
- Just copy off someone.
- I can't. It's all essays.
如果这门不过
我平均成绩就完了
If I fail this class,
my average is shot.
我可能会失去资助或勒令退学
I might lose my financial aid
or not be allowed back.
那么你就完蛋了
Well, you're fucked, then.
那来我的晚会，与贝思勾搭
愉快度过你最后一周
So come to my party, hook up
with Beth, and enjoy your last week.
我谁也不勾搭
我和v的关系是认真的
I'm not hooking up with anyone.
I'm invested in this relationship.
认真的？你是谁？
查尔斯你思瓦波？听着！
Invested? Who are you, Charles
Schwab? Listen to yourself!
与贝思春宵一度
I would give my life...
我死也在所不惜…
for one evening
of consensual sex with that girl.
我与v这么久也没欺骗过
I've gone this long without cheating.
你已经在欺骗了
You're already cheating!
每次你拒绝做爱
你都是在欺骗自己
Any time you pass up sex
you cheat yourself.
想想饮酒吸毒的机会
The window of opportunity
to drink and do drugs
沾女朋友便宜的机会日益减少
and take advantage
of young girls is shrinking daily.
我得打个电话
I gotta make a call.
我告诉你，放弃这个机会
你会遗恨终身
I'm telling you, you pass this up,
it'll haunt you forever.
你的老二不会原谅你的
Your dick will never forgive you.
你说呢？你不想有新经验吗？
What do you think, man? Don't you
want to experience something new?
做乔希的老二不容易啊
(Squeaky voice )
It ain't easy being Josh's penis.
来了两个月了
我感觉没一点儿意思
We've been here two months,
and I feel like I'm in a coma.
别闹了
我希望我是你的老二，EL
- Stop it.
- I wish I was your dick, EL.
再没刺激事儿，我就离开你了
If something doesn't happen soon,
I'm gonna leave.
够了
喂？
- Enough.
- (Girl) 'Hello?'
卡拉，是乔希，抱歉
v芬妮在吗？
Carla, it's Josh. Sorry to bother
you, is Tiffany around?
v芬妮不在
Tiffany is not here.
她昨夜…又没回来睡觉
She didn't sleep here
last night...again.
如果你能停止每小时来电
那就太好了
And it would be great
if for one hour you didn't call.
好
如果她想跟你通话
- Right.
- If she wanted to talk to you
她就会给你打的
she'd call you.
你就看着办吧
Deal with it.
臭婊子！
她听起来撩人吗？
- You bitch!
- Does she sound hot?
我们从未这么长时间不说话
一定出事了
We've never gone this long
without talking. Something's wrong.
她另有新欢了，你也应该如此
She found someone else,
like you should.
时间在流逝，转眼你就
四十岁了，找姑娘要付钱的
The clock is ticking. Before you know
it you'll be 40 and paying for girls.
我应该警告你
I should really warn you,
这会影响你的判断力
it's been known to affect
your decision-making abilities
降低你的抑制力
and lower your inhibitions.
好，这正是我之所求
Good. That's the plan.
不，那…正是所求
No, that-that's...
Yes, that is the plan.
你有现金吗？
干什么？
- You bring cash?
- Why?
我们有美女要出售
什么？
- We've got chicks for sale.
- What?
相信我，我在这学校呆了七年
Trust me. I've been goin'
to this school seven years
我知道全面大学教育的关键…
and I know the key
to a well-rounded college education
必须有试验精神
is experimentation.
我来示范
Let me show you.
这是拍卖，记住…
This is an auction. Remember...
你不是在买姑娘
you are not buying the girl,
只是买陪伴
买卖不包括与她上床
only her company, and sale does not
constitute sexual relations.
我知道，相信我，我试过
(EL) I know. Believe me, I've tried.
那就闲话少说，首先介绍…
Without further ado,
let's introduce our first...person.
劳拉！
- Laura!
- (Applause )
她来自长岛
Laura's from Long Island.
喜欢户外活动和吃海鲜
She likes the outdoors
and loves seafood.
你好，拍卖从五元开始
你三块五
- OK, let's start the bidding at $5!
- $3.50!
天啊，钱袋们
她不是麦当劳的儿童餐
Good God, moneybags,
she's not a Happy Meal.
五块
有人出五块，谁出十块？
- $5.
- OK, we've got five. Do I hear 10?
十块
- 10 bucks.
- (Auctioneer calling)
谁出十五与劳拉共度一晚？
Who's got 15 bucks
for a lovely evening with Laura?!
好，十五块，谁再加些？
十五块，一，二
OK, we got 15. Who can beat 15?
Going once, going twice...
卖给…队长了
Sold...to the captain.
你在这儿
There you are.
嗨，你在干什么？
没干什么
- Hey, what's going on?
- Not much.
你你真漂亮
你谢谢
- You look great.
- Thank you.
别客气
You're welcome.
听着，雅克布来了
他是个疯子
Listen, Jacob's here,
and he's a total psycho...
你可以叫赢他吗？
Can you go outbid him?
但我没带那么多钱
You know what,
I didn't bring that much money.
你不明白，他迷上我了
You don't understand. He's obsessed.
这很有趣，对吧？
See? That's fun, right?
好，现在我要你们互吻对方
OK, OK. Now, I want you two
to kiss each other.
有人见到贝思了吗？她在那儿
All right, has anyone seen Beth?
There she is!
贝思，对大家打个招呼
嗨
- (Cheering)
- Say hi to the crowd, Beth.
有人开价五块了吗？
Can I hear a $5 opening bid?
我出五块
谁能击败五块？
- $5 right here!
- Who can beat five?
七块
十块
- Seven.
- $10.
十块！一，二
十五块！
- $10! Going once. Going twice.
- $15!
二十块
二十五块！
- 20.
- 25!
二十五，谁能击败二十五？
25. Who can beat 25? Going once.
一，二
二十六
- Going twice.
- 26.
二十六，一
三十！
- 26, going once.
- 30!
好，谁来击败二十六？
我刚叫过三十
- OK, can anyone beat $26?
- I just said 30!
一定会有人击败二十六
There must be someone
who can beat $26?
我呀！在这儿，三十
卖给乔希二十六块
- Me, right here! 30!
- Sold! To my man Josh for $26.
你听到我高声叫喊三十块
You heard me.
I bid $30 loud and clear.
你的不算
Your bid didn't count.
为什么？
因为你是助教
- Why?
- Because you're a TA.
怎样啦？
这是学生的拍卖
- So?
- This auction is for students.
再见
Goodbye.
谢谢你，我欠你一个
Thanks for doing that. I owe you one.
欠我何止一个
是吗？
- You owe me more than one.
- Do I?
严格地说
Technically.
那…
Well...
你准备好提货了吗？
are you ready to collect?
对，准备好了
I think so. Yeah.
我们互相抚摸
We're touching.
非常有趣
It's a lot of fun. (Chuckles )
我们很开心
- We're having a good time.
- (Chuckles )
我想你爱你的v芬妮
(Romantic music)
v芬妮是谁？
Who's Tiffany Henderson?
我五岁开始约会的女孩
Just some girl I used to date
since I was, like, five.
现在散了，她蹬了我
But that's over now. She blew me off.
啊，可怜的孩子
Oh, poor baby.
你一定很难过
You must be very hurt.
你需要特别的照顾吗？
Do you need some special attention?
的确，我很难过
Well, I am pretty upset.
这样会好点儿吗？
Did that help?
好多了
That helped a lot.
我有个主意
I have an idea.
你说呢？
What do you say?
嗯，这不太好
Uh, I don't think so.
来！会很好玩
Come on! It'll be fun.
你我一直想试这个
你不…
- I've always wanted to try this.
- No...
来
Yes.
我来采访你
I'm gonna interview you.
可以
Fine.
好
OK.
你好，乔希
你好
- OK, Josh.
- Yes.
你喜欢什么样的女孩子？
What do you look for in a girl?
嗯，让我想想
Um, well, let's see.
她应当精明有趣…
She should be smart and funny and...
这也很不错
That's good, too.
现在觉得好点了吗？
Do you feel better yet?
好一点儿了，对，一点点儿
I feel a little bit better.
Yeah. A little...
你还喜欢什么？
What else do you look for?
她要漂亮…
She should be attractive and...
温柔…
nice and...
无上装，无上装
Topless. And topless.
还要吻我
And she should kiss me.
还有呢？
What else?
她不应该停止吻我
She shouldn't stop kissing me.
你为什么停下来？
Why don't you keep doing that?
小小三文鱼在溪中游动
# Tiny salmon swimming in a stream
小小三文鱼有非份之想
# Tiny salmon
chasing that impossible dream
八哥鸟说
# The mynah bird says
黑猩猩说
# The chimpanzee says
猫头鹰朋友说
# The friendly owl says
但三文鱼只会说
# But the salmon can only say
好可怜啊
# And it's sad #
早安，各位
# Good morning, everyone.
你好，你好，你好？
# How are you and you and you #
你为什么这么高兴？
What are you so happy about?
不知道，今早我像高兴吗？
I don't know.
Do I seem happy this morning?
对，你在这儿跳来跳去
Well, you're bouncing around here.
你确实看起来特别开心
You do seem
unusually light-hearted.
可能是昨夜
我度过了一生最好的夜晚
Maybe it's because I had
the best time of my life last night.
两次！今早又干了一次
Twice! And once this morning.
你和贝思？
You and Beth?
你啊，对
你住嘴，发生了什么事？
- Oh, yeah.
- Shut up. What happened?
不可能！你在撒谎
No way! You're lying.
我没有撒谎
I'm not lying.
你不能只应付了人家
可假装上了床
You can't make out with someone
then pretend you had sex.
你这不够潇洒
你我没有撒谎
- That's really uncool.
- I'm not pretending.
算了吧，我知道你在撒谎
我敢肯定
Forget it. I know you're lying.
I guarantee it.
要打赌吗？
You wanna bet?
好，我打赌，你没有证据
Great. I'm gonna bet
on something you can't prove.
你录下来了！
You videotaped it!
不，我没有，给我！给我！
No, no, no, I didn't!
Gimme that! Gimme that!
你不给，这太棒了
你我在开玩笑！
- No way! This is amazing!
- I was kidding, I was kidding!
把录像带给我
嗯？来吧
- Gimme the tape.
- Huh? Come on.
我们迟早会看到的
他说得对
- We're gonna see it sooner or later.
- He's got a point.
不，不，不！
Oh-ho! Oh, no! Oh, no!
给我，不，把它给我
Give it to me. No, give it to me.
-EL，不
乔希，别，我们需要它
- EL, no.
- Josh, please? We need this.
好，听着，你们别告诉其他人
OK, listen, seriously.
You can't tell anyone you saw this.
啊，好
Oh, yeah.
行，行！
OK. OK!
巴里，拉上窗帘
Barry, hit the lights.
是娱乐的时间了
It's boner time!
v，这是我从艾菲嘉直播
'Hey, Tif. It's me
coming to you live from Ithaca.'
我不是叫你昨天寄出了吗？
I thought I asked you
to mail this yesterday?
对，你说了，我今天寄出了
Yeah, you did. I mailed it today.
快速进到精彩部份
Fast-forward to the horny stuff.
你把这个寄给v芬妮了吗？
Is this the shit
you've been sending Tiffany?
啊，上帝
Oh, my God.
是你…
# It's you... #
啊，他妈的！
Oh, fuck!
啊，上帝，不，不，不
Oh, my God! No, no, no, no.
啊，上帝！
Oh, God!
等一等
W-wait a second.
你把贝思的带子寄给v芬妮了
Tell me you mailed
the Beth tape to Tiffany.
是啊！
Yes!
混蛋！啊！不，不！
Shit! Oh, no! Oh, no!
嗨，嗨
Hey, hey.
你有没有复制盘？
Did you make a copy?
有的话，我们可以看看
If you made a copy,
we could watch the copy.
别接！
Don't answer it!
嗨，这是乔希和鲁宾，请留言
(Answer machine ) 'Hey, it's
Josh and Rubin. Leave a message.'
嗨！乔希，这是v芬妮
'Hi, Josh. It's Tiffany.
抱歉没跟你通话
'Sorry we haven't spoken.
我外公去世了
'Listen, my grandfather passed away.
我打过几次电话了，都没人接
'I've tried calling you
a few times, but no one picked up.
我不想留这样的言给你
'I didn't want to leave
this message on your machine
但现在你可能会着急了…
'but by now you're probably
a little worried so...
现在我在家里帮助我妈
'Anyway, I'm at my parents'
house helping my mom.
她很伤心
'She's really a wreck.
如果联系不上
我星期一再来电话
'If I don't speak with you,
I'll call Monday.
我没事儿，只需要点儿时间
'I'll be OK. I just need some time.
再见，我爱你
'Bye. I love you.'
这不公平
That's not fair.
她有带子看而我们却看不到
How come she gets to see the tape
and we don't?
她星期一回校
我有三天的时间赶去
She gets back there Monday.
That leaves three days to get there.
去哪儿？奥斯丁？
Get where? Austin?
你到那儿有一万英里
你一千八百
- That's like 10,000 miles from here.
- 1,800.
三天赶一千八百英里？飞吧
You wanna drive 1,800 miles
in three days? Just fly.
你有钱买机票吗？我没有
Do you have money for a ticket?
I don't.
那好，我们开车
你去吗？
- All right, so we're driving.
- You're coming?
我留下来干什么？学习？
What else am I gonna do,
stay here and learn?
开车上路
Road trip.
等等，等一下儿
(Behind door) Just a minute. Hold on.
他可能在自渎
He's probably jackin' off.
你们想干什么？
What do you guys want?
凯尔，这是紧急情况
Kyle, this is an emergency.
等等，至少让我回去
打电话给我爸爸
Wait. Let me at least
go back and call my dad.
打电话给你爸爸？
你自己没主见？
Call your dad?
Would you listen to yourself?
你十九岁了！
怎么还他妈的娘娘腔？
You're 19 years old,
and you're a fucking sissy.
只知道坐在图书馆猜迷
All you ever do is sit
in a library and play Myst.
这真可怜
It's pathetic.
他是说这是你做大事的好机会
He's trying to say that
this is your chance to do something.
去冒险吧，跟我们一起去
Be a risk-taker. Come with us.
你们这样说，不过是要我的车
You're just saying that
because you want my car.
不，我们一直都很喜欢你
No! No, we've always liked you.
或把车借给我们，这也是冒险
Or just give us the car.
That would make him a risk-taker.
闭嘴，行吗？他也一起去
Shut up, all right?
He's coming with us.
来呀，凯尔，会非常好玩
Come on, Kyle. It'll be fun!
你不想知道我们去哪儿吗？
Aren't you even curious
where we're going?
不想
No.
我们去奥斯丁大学
你不想去吗？
OK, we're going to the University
of Austin. Sure you won't come?
我不喜欢麻省
I don't like Massachusetts.
奥斯丁在德州，波士顿在麻省
Austin's in Texas.
You're thinking of Boston.
你从未离开这个城市，对吧？
You've never left this town,
have you?
没有
No, not really.
这样会憋出恐惧症的
That could turn
into a debilitating phobia.
好吧
OK.
我可以喂米切吗？
是的，你当然可以
- Can I feed Mitch?
- Yes, actually you can.
笼子旁边有个装老鼠的灰盒子
There's a brown box of mice
by his cage.
明天给它一只，就一只
Give him one tomorrow. Just one.
我明天喂它一只老鼠
好
- I'll feed him a mouse tomorrow.
- OK.
你可以信任我，我很可靠
You can count on me.
OK? I'm reliable. OK?
你们一路顺风，安全愉快
You guys do good.
Have a good trip, safe trip.
扣好安全带，我明天喂蛇
Buckle up your seat belt.
I'm gonna feed the snake!
我明天喂蛇，照顾蛇
I'll feed the snake,
I'll watch the snake.
这样他们就出发了
(Barry ) 'So off they went.'
三日里要赶一千八百英里
They had 1,800 miles to go,
and only three days to do it.
这是个疲劳的旅程
彻底改变了他们的一生
It was a killer journey and one
that changed them all forever.
完了
The end.
你我们到那儿看看
你哇，就这些？这故事真混帐
- So we're gonna go look over here.
- Whoa. That's it? This story sucks.
录相带怎么样了？
啊，录像带
- What happened with the tape?
- Right. The tape.
唔…
Well, um...
就像我说的，他们与时间赛跑
Well... Like I said,
they were on a race against time.
星期五下午1:08纽约州界
# The smoke stack spitting black soot
into the sooty sky
我们没看到带子
Since we didn't get to see the tape,
你说给我们听听，好吗？
你不
- can you at least describe it?
- No.
至少承认贝思很出色
Admit that Beth is amazing.
我承认，她很出色，很完美
I admit it, she's amazing.
She's perfect.
不知道你为何内疚
严格地讲，这不算欺骗
I don't know why you feel so guilty.
Technically you haven't cheated.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
男人关于欺骗的理解
There are these rules that guys have,
有他们自己的规矩
an understanding
as to what constitutes cheating.
就拿你的情况来说吧
Take your situation, for example.
这不算欺骗
It's not cheating.
因为你在另一个地区－
更别说另一个州了
Not when you're in a different
area code - not to mention state!
这毫无道理
That makes no sense.
别看着我，规矩不是我定的
Don't look at me, Kyle.
I don't make the rules.
这是正常的，我看过一篇文章
This is legit. I've read an article.
这些规矩多的是，都是歪理
There's a whole bunch of them,
like loopholes.
比如说一脚踏两只船
Say you were sleeping with
two girls at the same time,
这不是欺骗
因为她们互相抵消了
it's not cheating
because they cancel each other out.
千真万确
- Ahh.
- Exactly!
或者你太笨了记不住
Or if you're too wasted
to remember...
这也不算欺骗
It is not cheating.
既然真的忘了
Because if you
can't really remember it,
那就是没真正发生过
it never really took place.
我也有个比如，准备好了吗？
OK, I've got one. Ready?
在你的尻丸上涂上花生酱
It's OK if you spread peanut butter
on your testicles
让你的狗去舔也没什么
and let your dog lick it off.
因为那是你的狗
上帝！
- Because it's your dog!
- Jesus Christ!
因为狗是你的
我们知道了
- You know, because it's your dog!
- We got it.
明天有人就要死了
Somebody's gonna die tomorrow.
对，你们中的一个要死了
That's right.
One of you is marked for death.
明天一大清早
And first thing tomorrow morning,
你们中的一个
a chosen one
will experience nature's wrath
将受到大自然愤怒的惩罚
in all its fury.
你是谁？
Who are you?
贝思
I'm Beth.
你来看喂蛇？
Are you here for the feeding?
对不起
Excuse me?
你来早了，明天才喂
You're early. It's not till tomorrow.
你应该来看
You should come back.
那将血流成河
It's gonna be a bloodbath.
我想免了吧
I think I'll pass.
你见过乔希了吗？
Have you seen Josh?
他去看他女朋友了
He went to visit his girlfriend.
v芬妮？
Tiffany?
我以为他们散了呢
I thought they broke up.
我是说这个女的是他朋友
你明白我的意思
I mean this girl who's a friend
of his. You know what I mean.
他去哪儿了？
Where did he go?
奥斯丁
Austin?
麻省的奥斯丁
Austin, Massachusetts?
你是说麻省的波士顿？
You mean Boston, Massachusetts?
对，我说的是波士顿
Yeah, that's what I said. Boston.
麻省的波士顿大学
The University of Boston
in Massachusetts.
他真是个混蛋
He is such an asshole.
他竟然当着我的面撒谎
I can't believe
he just lied to my face like that.
我还以为他喜欢我呢
他怎么能这样做？
I actually thought he liked me.
How could he do that?
她光着上身？
女孩子不会脱光的
- She was topless?
- Girls don't stand around naked.
她们会的，这是我的故事
你们到底听不听？
Yeah, they do. OK? This is my story.
You wanna hear it or not?
这不…
嘘，别打叉，好吗？
- It just doesn't make any...
- Shh. Please, no interruptions, OK?
因此另一个女孩走来，很刺激
So this other girl walks up,
totally hot. Naked! Really naked!
裸体！完全光着！
我知道男人会很坏
I know guys can be jerks.
但我以为乔希不同，我喜欢他
I guess I just thought
Josh was different. I liked him.
亲爱的，听我说，他们都一样
Sweetie, listen to me.
They're all the same.
男人都是变态的猪
All men are perverted pigs.
他们真正关心的…
脑子里想的只有性
All they care about...
really, all they THINK about is sex.
你一点不错，我感到被利用了
你面对它吧，我们都一样
- You're so right. I feel so used.
- Face it, we're all used.
在大部分男人的眼里
我们只是肉体
In most men's eyes, we're just flesh.
真恶心！
是恶心，想一想
- It's so sick!
- It IS sick. Think about it.
如果他们那样…
If they had it their way...
我甚至不愿去想会发生什么
God, I don't even want to know
what would happen
如果他们那样去做！
if they had it their way!
他走了，我该怎么办？
(Beth) What am I supposed to do
now that he's gone?
你该去波士顿揍他屁股
对
- Go to Boston and bust his ass.
- Right.
面对他和他的女朋友
Confront him
and his little girlfriend.
面对他们，你应当面对他们
Face to face. You totally should!
告诉她乔希是个混蛋，对吧？
Show her what an asshole Josh is,
right?
这个，也是
Ooh! These, too.
凯尔，过来一下儿
Kyle, come here for a second.
我们的现金不够
We're a little
short on cash right now,
要借用一下儿你的信用卡
so we need to put this
on your credit card.
我保证回校后还你钱
We'll give you the cash
when we get back, I promise.
不行，那是我爸爸的
是应急用的
I can't. It's my dad's.
It's for emergencies only.
嗨，现在就是应急啊
Hello! This IS an emergency.
我们需要这些东西
你要我们睡大街上？
We need this stuff.
You want us to sleep in the dirt?
我们在一个无人之地
(Josh) We're in no-man's-land.
在这条路上跑了一个多小时
We've been on this road
for over an hour.
这起码能节省我们五个小时
This is gonna save us five hours,
minimum. Thank me later.
我们应当回到大路去
We should go back to the interstate.
我们不回头
对，相信我
- We're not goin' back.
- Yeah, have some faith.
这是挑战，所以叫捷径
It's a challenge.
That's why it's a short cut.
如果容易就叫大路了
If it was easy,
it would just be the way.
该死！他妈的！
(Josh) Damn it! Fuck!
我想二十分钟后
有人就会来鸡奸我们
I give us 20 minutes
before our first ass-raping.
如果掉头会失去五个小时
If we turn around we'll lose
five hours backtracking.
掉头？就因为这个？
我们可以解决
Turn around? Why? Because of this?
We could make it.
解决？你是说跳过去？
Make it? You mean jump it?
不，绝对不行，我们掉头
No. Absolutely not.
No way. We're going back.
可以成功的
这个斜度大概是三十度
It can be done. This incline
is 30 degrees roughly, right?
车身重一千六百磅
The factory weight
of the car is 1,600lbs.
加上我们和行李…
Add us, plus cargo...
不，不
如果车时速为五十英里
- No, no.
- If we hit this at 50mph,
弹道很容易超过十英尺
our trajectory
will clear 10 feet, easy.
不行，绝对不行
No way. Absolutely not.
为保险起见，我们开六十英里
We'll go 60 just to be certain.
我们掉头吧，这没门儿
(Kyle ) We're goin' back.
It's impossible.
你肯定能行？
You sure?
当然，物理我在行
With physics I'm always sure.
我来开车
I'm driving.
我想你们没听到我的话
I don't think you guys heard me.
这是我的车，我们不跳河
This is my car
and we're not gonna jump any rivers.
凯尔，才十英尺
高尔夫球车也能跳过
Kyle, it's 10 feet. Bob Hope
could jump this in a golf cart.
瞧，我都可以吐口水过去
Look, I can spit across this gap.
好
Yeah.
我们…
Well...
还是开七十五吧
better make it 75.
来，我们冲
凯尔，相信我，这是科学
- OK. Let's do it.
- Trust me, Kyle, it's science.
不，你们不能，EL，你出来
No, you guys. No.
EL, get out of my car.
凯尔，进来，快点儿
Kyle, in the car. Come on.
准备好了
We're OK.
要开六十英里，知道吗？
You know we need to hit 60?
你我正在努力，这车不行
你停下！
- I'm trying. This car sucks.
- Stop!
谢谢你！好！
(EL) Thank you! Yes!
我早就说过了
What did I tell you?
啊，上帝！
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
我爸爸知道了，一定会杀了我
My father is gonna kill me
when he finds out about this.
我只说过我们可以跳过去
I only said we'd make it across.
没说过车轮会没事儿
I never said
the wheels would stay on.
我们现在怎么办？
What the hell are we gonna do now?!
我完了
I'm totally screwed!
我没有时间…走出…树林
I don't have time...
to be walking...through the woods!
我们叫拖车来，把轴修好
Josh, we'll call a tow truck,
have the axles fixed.
不过是车轮，最多半天便修好
We'll lose half a day at most.
It's just the wheels.
每当我对某人产生感情时
(Beth) The minute I think
I feel something for someone,
他们都会掉头来伤害我
they just turn around
and screw me over.
但乔希不同，他很特别
Just something about Josh,
he's just different.
我觉得我们有感应
I feel like we had a connection.
我想我再也不信任男人了
I don't think
I'll ever be able to trust a guy.
对，不要信
我最后一次信任男人是1985年
You shouldn't! Honey, the last time
I trusted a man was back in 1985
他开着我的车跟我妹妹跑了
and he took off
with my sister and my van.
那是个大车，不像这个小破车
It was a regular-size van.
Before that mini-van crap.
那么没希望了，嗯？
So there's no hope, huh?
啊，有，但是电动的
Oh, there's hope.
But it comes with batteries.
你留着用吧
You can keep that.
天呀
(Kyle ) God. Crap.
大家听着，我们得小心点儿
(EL) Listen, guys,
we're gonna have to be more careful.
刚才差点没命了
We almost died in that explosion.
你我倒希望我死了
你不是开玩笑，我不能早逝
- I wish I had died.
- I'm serious. I can't die young.
我有种感觉，人类将需要我
Something tells me the people
of Earth are gonna need me.
我必须活下去
I must live.
对，我们都要活下去
Yeah, right. We all must live.
但首先我们必须回到大路上
Before we do that,
we must get back on the road.
我们不应该现在睡觉
(Josh) We shouldn't be going
to sleep right now!
在这儿，那儿都处理一下…
'Let's just lay
an indication here and there.'
涂上各种颜色…
(TV) 'And a whole bunch of colour...'
对不起
Excuse me.
抱歉，你不要接电话吗？
I'm sorry, do you need to get that?
你有什么事儿吗？
Do you need something?
对，这是个特殊的问题
Yeah.
This is sort of an unusual question.
你有大麻卖点儿给我吗？
But do you have any marijuana
I might buy?
昨晚我们的车炸了
我一点儿都没有了
Our car exploded last night
and I'm practically all out.
我像个毒贩子吗？
Am I a drug dealer?
不，我不是，谢谢你问我
No, I am not.
Thank you for asking, though.
没有，那好，谢谢
No? OK, that's OK. Thanks.
你还需要别的吗？
Is there anything else
I can help with?
比如要一个十一岁的妓
我们可以帮助
Perhaps you'd like an 11-year-old
prostitute. We can do that.
或者帮你杀掉谁，嗯？
Or maybe we can off someone
for you. Huh?
我明白了，我们该从小事做起
I've got it.
Why don't we start small?
想要条新毛巾吗？
Would you like a fresh towel?
你可以起来吸
You could roll that up and smoke it.
鬼
Dick.
还有，小伙子
By the way, Cheech,
你们那张信用卡超额了
that credit card
you guys gave me was maxed out,
别把钱都花在毒品和枪枝上
so don't go spending all your cash
on needles and guns just yet.
厄尔你爱德华先生？
Um, Mr Earl Edwards?
对不起，先生，你的卡超额了
I'm sorry, sir.
This card's over its limit.
不会的，你拿回去再试一次
That's not true. Put it through
your little machine again.
我试过三次了
如果你还有另一个卡，我…
I tried three times, sir. If you
have another card, I'd be happy to...
别装腔作势
Don't give me any attitude.
你去把那鬼机器好好修修
You go fix
that little toy back there,
把账记在卡上
and charge this friggin' card.
我们是这里二十年的顾客了
We've been coming here for 20 years.
我们才开张了八年
马上去做
- We've only been open eight years.
- Do it now.
别紧张，没什么大不了的
(EL) Relax, it's not a big deal.
你不明白，乔希知道会发疯的
(Rubin ) You don't understand,
when Josh finds out he'll freak.
没有信用卡不能租车
You can't rent a car without
a credit card. You just can't.
那么，我们怎么办？
So, what are we gonna do?
这样吧，你呆在这儿
Tell you what. Stay here.
带他去吃早餐或什么的
Take him out
for breakfast or something.
那事儿包在我身上
I'll go take care of this.
厄尔，库克，出了点儿事
你们保持静
Earl, Cookie, we have a situation.
Now, brace yourselves.
警方在宾州贝德佛
找到了凯尔的车
The police have found Kyle's car
abandoned in Bedford, Pennsylvania.
车炸成了碎片
It's been blown to bits.
我们问过他的学校了－
他失踪了
We checked with the university -
he's missing.
上帝啊
Mother of God.
你早上好
你嗨
- (Woman ) Good morning.
- Hello.
嗨，你有什么事儿吗？
Hi. How can I help you?
嗨，我是派来检查111巴士的
Yeah, hi. I was sent over here
to check out bus 111,
恐怕情况不妙
and I'm afraid I have some bad news.
旋转片…出现了问题
You seem to be having problems
with the...rotator splint.
引擎有旋转片吗？
Engines have rotator splints?
有
Yeah.
车现在没事，但很快就不行了
She runs good now, but not for long.
我可以一周后修好送回来
I can have it back to you
as good as new in a week.
让我看看，贾德还在阿城
Let's see.
Well, Jared's still in Aliquippa,
他在那儿给你打的电话？
对
- I take it he called you from there?
- Yeah.
五天吧，五天应该没问题
Five days.
Well, I think we can work that out.
你别喂我的狗好吗？
Would you please not feed my dog?
我没喂
I didn't.
你不能喂向导狗
You can't feed
Seeing Eye dogs treats.
你不骚扰它我会很感激的
I'd appreciate it
if you left him alone.
别对我瞪眼
Don't roll your eyes at me.
油炸面包
French toast.
咸肉，好东西
Bacon. Good for you.
你还有炒蛋
你谢谢
- And scrambled eggs.
- Thank you.
对不起，这上面有糖
我点的是无糖的
Excuse me, but this has powdered
sugar on it, and I ordered no sugar.
我早上不能吃太多的糖
I can't have
too much sugar in the morning.
噢，对不起，你说得真对
Oh, I'm sorry,
you're absolutely right.
这样吧，我拿回去
再给你换新的
Tell you what, let me take this back
and bring you out a new piece.
没问题吧？好，太好了
Is everybody good? OK, great.
谁看到我的书了？我找不…
Do you know where my possessions are,
because I can't...
等等，不，在车上
那…太好笑了
- Wait, no. They were in the car.
- That's...that's hilarious.
好，我给你加点儿
All right,
let me warm that up for you.
你给你
你谢谢
- There you go.
- Thanks.
对不起，油炸面包马上就来
Excuse me. And the French toast
will be out in just a minute.
好，谢谢
好，太好了
- OK, thank you.
- OK, great.
油炸面包，无糖的
French toast, no sugar.
你行吗？真是对不起
你没关系
- All right? Sorry about that.
- No problem.
他真是个好人
That's a nice guy.
很好吃
It's good.
我不想知道你是怎样弄来的
I don't wanna know
how you got this.
从盲妞儿那儿偷来的
我不想知道
- I stole it from a blind chick.
- I don't wanna know.
什么，我会还给她的
What? I'm gonna give it back.
或许吧
Probably.
请马上停车好吗？我要上厕所
Can we please stop soon?
I need to use the bathroom.
我不急着上，再等两个小时吧
Actually, I don't have to go yet,
so we'll stop in a couple of hours.
我开玩笑，凯尔，我们停车
I'm kidding, Kyle. We'll stop.
老天，你要维护自己的权利
坚定点儿
Jeez, you have to stand up
for yourself. Be more assertive.
对
OK.
你怎么会这样？你怕什么？
What's your deal?
Why are you so worried?
我不知道，可能是我爸爸
I don't know. I guess it's my dad.
他…他很严厉
He's, like...strict.
他发现了车子的事
一定不会饶过我的
He really is gonna kill me
when he finds out about that car.
你搞砸了，妙极了
谁都会出错
So you screwed up. Big deal.
People make mistakes.
他会接受事实的
再说，那是部烂车
He'll get over it.
Besides, that car sucked anyways.
我真的要上厕所了
I really do need
to go to the bathroom.
我们在加油站停车
又停车？
- (EL) We're makin' a pit stop.
- (Rubin ) Again?!
你将亲身经历…
You're about to experience
first-hand...
食物链下游地位意味着什么
exactly what it means to be in
the lower region of the food chain.
米切就要咬你
Mitch is going to bite into you.
挤压你
He's going to squeeze.
实际上你还没死
它就开始消化你
He'll actually start digesting you
while you're still alive.
但不要害怕
But don't be scared.
别害怕
No. No, no.
这将是个快速死亡
It'll be a quick death.
要勇敢
Be brave.
你不会感到痛的
You'll barely feel it.
来
Come on.
来，你妈的怎么不吃它？
Come on. You gonna fuckin' eat him?
乔希，等等
Josh, wait up a second.
我们是上路开眼界
This is supposed to be a road trip.
但却一味地开车，太荒谬了
All we do is drive the whole time.
It's ridiculous.
你没人逼你来
你我们玩得不错
- No one forced you to come.
- We're making great time.
如果v芬妮看到录相带
那是件好事
And if Tiffany saw that tape,
it'd be a good thing.
你这是什么意思？
What is that supposed to mean?
贝思就像是天使
她来帮你改变你的一生
Beth is an angel. She's here
to help you change your life.
再说，v芬妮会让你拍她吗？
Besides, did Tiffany
ever let you videotape her?
我想不会
I think not.
这是征兆，乔希
It's a sign, Josh.
你喂？
你安迪生教授吗？
- 'Professor Anderson?'
- Who's calling?
你是谁？
嗨，教授，我是乔希你帕克
Hi, Professor, it's Josh Parker.
嗨，乔希，你有什么事？
(Deeper voice ) Hello, Josh.
What can I do for you?
你我遇上了交通事故了
你啊，天啊
- Well, I was in a car accident.
- 'Oh. Oh, my God.'
我没事儿，就是有点儿困难
I'm OK.
It's just I'm in kind of a bind.
我的书和笔记都毁掉了
All my notes and books
were destroyed.
我能不能申请延期？
Is it possible to get an extension?
过两天再考期中考试？
'Maybe take the mid-term
a couple days later?'
啊，行啊，这是紧急情况
Oh, sure.
Yes, it sounds like an emergency.
延迟三天怎么样？
How about an extra three days?
这可以了吧？
这太好了？
- 'Would that work?'
- Yeah, that would be fantastic!
你真的可以吗？
你没事儿我就放心了
- Are you sure?
- 'Just glad you're not hurt.'
我现在就记下来
I'm marking it down right now.
太好了，教授，谢谢你
'That's great, Professor. Thank you.'
好，再见
OK, goodbye.
是谁啊？
Who was that?
乔希你帕克
Oh, that...that was Josh Parker.
啊，是吗？他有什么事儿？
Oh, yeah? What did he want?
只想核实一下考试的时间
他太紧张了
He was just confirming
the date of the exam. Such a worrier.
宾夕尼亚贝德佛
(Siren wails)
没事儿，我会找到他的
It's gonna be OK. I'll find him.
也会找出肇事者，不会有事的
And we'll find whoever did this,
I promise. It's gonna be OK.
我推测这儿有人遭到奸杀
If I had to guess, I'd say somebody
was raped and murdered here.
你怎么会有这种想法？
What the hell gives you that idea?
不知道，凭感觉
I don't know. It's just a feeling.
你怎么样？
你没什么
- Well?
- Nothing yet.
幸运的是没有挣扎过的迹象
Good thing is,
there's no evidence of a struggle.
没有血迹和衣服等等
No blood or clothing or anything.
也没有发现一滴精液
And we haven't found
a single drop of semen yet.
星期六上午11：12
波士顿
嗨，我从家里来看朋友
Hi. I'm visiting my friend from home.
她不知道我来，想给她个惊喜
But she doesn't know I'm coming.
It's a surprise.
真妙，我能帮你点儿什么？
How nice. How can I help you?
我是第一次来，不知她住哪儿
I've never been here before.
I don't know where she lives.
她叫什么名字？我给你查查
What's her name? I can look it up.
啊，v芬妮你安迪森
Oh, OK. Tiffany Henderson.
我认识你吗？
Do I know you?
不，但我认识你的男朋友
No, you don't.
Actually, I know your boyfriend.
好，你是谁？
OK. Who are you?
我叫贝思，我们坐下谈好吗？
I'm Beth.
Could we just sit down for a minute?
好
OK.
嗯，我不知道该怎么开口
Um, this is really hard for me,
但有件事你一定要知道
but it's definitely
something you should hear.
你的男朋友在欺骗你…他跟我
Your boyfriend is cheating on you...
with me.
星期四晚上我们在一起
We were together Thursday night.
两次
Twice.
星期五早上又一次
And once again Friday morning.
我想你应该知道
I thought you should know.
对不起
Sorry.
v芬妮！你他妈的在干什么？
Tiffany! What the hell are you doing?
他是谁？
她的男朋友
- Who's that guy?
- That's her boyfriend.
她的男朋友？
THAT's her boyfriend?
对，他欺骗她
Yeah. He's been cheating on her.
宝贝，我爱你！
(Boyfriend) Baby, I love you!
星期六下午7：3690号公路
(Thuds and groans )
对不起
I-I'm sorry,
但你的脚太美了
but you have the most beautiful feet.
你想按摩一下儿脚吗？
Ohh... Would you like
a foot massage?
不，我不想按摩脚
No, I would not like a foot massage.
事实际上，我憎恨足部按摩
(Louder voice ) I would hate
a foot massage!
啊，对不起，别紧张
OK. I'm sorry. Relax.
还有没有正常的男人了！啊？
Are there any guys out there
who are just normal? ! Huh?!
米切，释放你的狂怒
- (Plucks string)
- Unleash the fury, Mitch.
释放你的狂怒
- (Plucks string)
- Unleash the fury.
来，米切
- Come on, Mitch.
- (Plucks string)
吃它
Eat him.
米切，求你，去吃它吧
Please, Mitch. Go get him, boy.
它就在那儿，杀死它
He's right there. Kill him.
伤它，咬它
Maim him. Bite him.
释放你的野性！
UNLEASH THE FURY!
星期六晚上8：12田纳西大学
噢，这真有趣
Wow, this is cool.
我从未到过兄弟会的地方
I've never been in
a fraternity house before.
真行得通吗？
Is this gonna work?
当然行得通，我懂得手势
Of course it's gonna work.
I know the handshake.
嗨
Hi.
你嗨，有什么事吗？
你对
- Hi. Can I help you?
- Yeah.
我是卡尔你鲁宾
艾菲嘉大学兄弟会的
I'm Rubin Carver,
a Xi Chi brother from Ithaca.
我们路过此地
想找个地方玩玩儿
We're just passing through
and looking for a place to party,
或许能住上一夜
maybe even a place to crash.
啊哼，啊，各位，这是鲁宾
Ahem. Uh, everyone, this is Rubin.
显然鲁宾是艾菲嘉分部的兄弟
Apparently, Rubin is our fraternity
brother from our Ithaca chapter.
这些是他的朋友
These are his friends.
我们打断你们吃饭了，我们…
Listen, uh, we've interrupted
your dinner so we'll just...
嗨，别傻了
Hey, don't be crazy.
这儿有足够的饭菜
There's plenty of food to go around.
欢迎你们留下
You guys are welcome to stay.
这饭菜还真不错
You know, this food's pretty good.
你知道这是黑人兄弟会吗？
Hey, you do realise
this is a national black fraternity?
他们知道你不是成员
They know you're not a member.
抱歉，我没有考虑过
I'm sorry. I don't think
about that kind of stuff.
别担心，他们只是跟我们玩玩
OK, relax. OK?
They're just messing with us.
他们很生气，因为他撒谎
They're pissed because he lied.
你我说我们走吧
你嘘，放松
- I say we get out of here.
- Shh, relax.
有人要解释一下儿
Someone's got some explaining to do.
你从他包里找到的
你什么？！那是什么？！
- Look what we found in his bag.
- What?! What is that?!
不，我从未见过那东西！
No, I've never seen that before!
你们来干什么？是三K党吗？
What are you doin'?
Are you in the Ku Klux Klan?
你啊，那不是我们的
你那不是我的
- Whoa, whoa. That is not ours.
- That's not mine!
好，等等，一定有原因的
OK, hold on, th-there's
obviously some explanation.
对，有原因，你们有偏见
现在要处死他了
Yeah, there is. See, your boy's
an evil bigot and now he's gonna die.
公正
Justice!
凯尔，凯尔
(Josh) Kyle. Kyle.
凯尔！
Kyle!
你醒了，还以为你死了
There you are. I thought we lost you.
你这是医院吗？
你你晕过去了
- Am I in the hospital?
- You passed out.
他们在逗我们，这是个玩笑
They were messin' with us, Kyle.
It was a joke.
种族主义者？
我常看黑人电视节目
Racist?
But I watch Oprah Winfrey every day.
跟你开玩笑，傻瓜
It was a joke, outtie. A joke!
我明白了
把三K党帽.子放进我包里
- (Laughing continues )
- I get it.
对，啊，真有趣
Yeah. Oh, that's funny.
我要杯冰镇酒
I need a wine cooler.
你喝我的吧
你谢谢
- Hey, have mine.
- Thanks.
他真是个可爱的小家伙
Isn't he just
the cutest little thing?
啊，凯尔是个好样的！
Oh, yeah, Kyle's the man!
你从未有过？一次也没有？
You mean never? Not even once?
我是说…有过
Well... I mean, I've had sex before.
但是…不是与人
Just, um,
明白了
Right.
噢…我觉得那很潇洒
Well, I think that's kinda cool.
你真的？
你真的
- You do?
- Yeah.
我是说你应该忍耐
第一次应该很特别
I mean, you should hold out.
It should be special.
有了爱情再做
Wait till you're in love.
我想我爱你
I think I love you.
你真可爱
You are so cute.
我想你没有避孕套
I take it you don't have a condom?
没有，我用光了
Um, I guess I'm all out.
噢，劳伦斯应该有
Well, Lawrence probably has some.
拉开那个抽屉看看
Why don't you try that drawer?
在香水旁边，皮带后面
Next to the Old Spice,
behind the belts.
猜对了
Good guess.
你知道吗？
You know what?
我不太清楚…我在做什么…
Um, I don't exactly know
what I'm doing and, um...
我…
I'm... Oof.
放松，宝贝儿，让朗达照顾你
Shhh. Relax, baby.
Let Rhonda handle this.
你谢谢，我很开心
你保重
- Thanks for a great time.
- Take care.
保持静
Stay cool.
嗨，德文
Hey, Devon.
怎么啦？
What's up?
田纳西州盟菲斯
凯尔，详细招来
发生了什么事？
Let's go, Kyle.
We want details. What happened?
我们喝了几杯酒
Well, we had a few drinks,
跳了会儿舞，你知道…
danced a little, and, you know...
我们不知道，快告诉我们
No, we don't know.
Why don't you tell us?
这是什么？你杀了个小妞？
Did you kill a cheetah?
是她的内裤，她送给我的
What? No. These are her underwear.
She gave 'em to me.
我干了她
I boinked her!
干了她？
Boinked?
你刚才说“干了”吗？
Yeah, did you just say
the word "boinked?"
凯尔，希望你别再想干了
I hope you got the boinking
out of your system,
今天我们要赶很长的路
cos we got a lot of driving
to do today.
别奢望去探访猫王故居
Do not get your hopes up
about visiting Graceland,
因为我们有重要任务
cos we're about the mission at hand.
你乔希
你什么事？
- Josh.
- What?
计划不错，但有个小问题
That sounds like a good plan,
except for one little thing.
你什么小问题？
你我们没钱了
- What little thing?
- We're out of money.
填表前我先问你们几个问题
OK, before you fill out these,
I have to ask some questions.
合格的话才可以捐精
If you qualify, you can
make a sperm deposit. Understood?
问吧
Mm-hmm. Fire away.
老实回答，否则没有报酬
你们骗不过检验
Tell the truth, because if you don't
the test will and you won't get paid.
在过去的36个小时内
有没有用过药.物？
So, first off, have any of you
done any drugs in the past 36 hours?
这也包括大麻
And that includes marijuana.
好，下个是
(Nurse ) OK, next.
在过去的24小时内
有没有性行为或自渎？
Have any of you had sex
or masturbated in the past 24 hours?
那，我不合格
Well, I guess I'm out.
因为我昨晚性交过…
Because I had sex last night...
跟一个女孩子！
with a girl! (Grunting)
这很好
That's nice.
文件夹里有你们需要的一切
You'll find everything you need
in these binders.
你们每人拿个杯子
Would you each take a cup.
你好
你这是你的
- OK.
- And yours.
完事后请送回来
I'd appreciate it if you'd
return those after you're finished.
好，谢谢
OK. Uh, thanks.
谢谢
Cheers.
对不起，有亚洲女人的吗？
Excuse me. Do you have anything
with Asian women?
我很喜欢亚洲妹
这里面却没有
I have this thing for Asian chicks,
and there's none here.
这儿不是窥视院
我们的材料有限
This isn't Peep World.
Our selection is limited.
你你凑合着干吧
你好
- You're gonna have to make do.
- OK.
你已经帮我不少了
You've been more than helpful.
有什么问题吗？
Is something wrong?
噢，没有
Well, no.
但…我感觉到…
But...I just couldn't help
but notice that...
我们之间有点儿什么？
Is there something between us?
我想，或者你可以…
I mean, I was thinking
that maybe you might want to...
我不知道…给我一点…
I don't know...
help me out with a little...
转业辅导？
professional assistance?
你需要我帮忙吗？
Do you need some help?
对，我需要
Yes, I do.
莫里斯大夫，请拨118
(Woman on PA)
'Dr Morris, dial 1-1-8, please.
莫里斯大夫，请拨118
'Dr Morris, please dial 1-1-8.'
我一看见你，便觉得你真棒
The moment I saw you out there,
I thought you were incredible.
你跟我认识的女孩不一样
你是真正的女人
You're not like most of the girls
I know. You're a woman.
好，转过身，脱下裤子
双手放在床上
That's fine. Turn around, drop your
pants, hands flat on the table.
哎哟，天啊
(Chuckling) Oh, my God.
你太好了，这样？
你对
- This is great. Wow. Like this?
- Exactly.
我得坦白，我喜欢你穿制服
(Sighs ) I have to admit,
I love you in that uniform.
你的丝袜到腰还是到大腿？
Do those nylons go all the way up,
or are they, like thigh high?
我要开始挤压前列腺
I'm gonna perform a procedure
called milking the prostate.
是从肛门引导射精
It's an anally-induced ejaculation.
肛门？
Anal?
你的直肠会感到有压力
You're gonna feel strong pressure
from inside your rectum.
来，你别跟我讲科学，宝贝儿
Come on, you don't have
to get all scientific, baby.
我是说，我们可以谈…
停下！好，继续干！
Stop! OK, keep doin' it. Yaaah!
就那儿！
(EL) Right there! Ahhh!
啊，天啊！
Oh, my God! Ohhh!
好，完事了
OK. All done.
这好厉害！
That was awesome!
等等，真的可以吗？
Wait. Wait. Does that work?
我是说，医学上真有可能吗？
I mean,
is it even medically possible?
对，当然可以
Oh, yeah, it works.
万试万灵
It works like a charm.
继续讲故事吧
But back to our story.
这是艾嘉菲星期天早上
'It was Sunday morning
back in Ithaca,
情况急转直下
'when things suddenly took
an unexpected turn.'
我是老鼠，吃我，吃我
(Barry ) I'm a mouse.
I'm a mouse. Eat me. Eat me.
吃我，吃我，吃我
Eat me. Eat me. Eat me.
Eat me. Eat me.
来啊
(Sighs ) Come on.
米切，你不吃，我要吃了
You better eat him, Mitch,
before I do.
它味道很好
(Panting) He's tasty.
米切，它味道很好
He's tasty, Mitch. Oh! Oh!
嗯！
Mmm! Mmm!
你为什么骗我？
- Mmm! Mmm!
- Why'd you lie to me?
我没有
(Gulps ) I didn't lie.
你说乔希去波士顿了
You-you told me
that Josh went to Boston.
你我没说，我说奥斯丁
你你说波士顿
- I didn't. I said Austin.
- You said Boston.
因为你，一个人的一生毁掉了
Because of you,
some guy's life is ruined.
那又怎样？无论他去了哪儿
都是因为你
So what? Besides, wherever he went,
he went because of you.
你什么意思，因为我？
你这还不明摆着
- What do you mean, because of me?
- Look, it's obvious.
乔希喜欢你，令人作呕
Josh likes you. It's disgusting.
我知道你会回来的
I knew you'd come back.
你你想干什么？
你跟乔希玩得怎么样？
- What do you want?
- So, how was your getaway with Josh?
你我没有
你当然没有，那没关系
- I wasn't with Josh.
- Sure. Doesn't matter, though.
因为他下学期不会来了
Cos Josh won't be back next semester.
他的哲学就要不及格了
He's about to flunk philosophy.
你你在说什么？
你他以为可以延期考试
- What are you talking about?
- He thinks that he has an extension,
但由于…某人，我
but thanks to
a...certain someone - me -
他不能延期
he doesn't.
你他是个白痴
你你是个疯子
(Jacob ) He's an idiot.
(Beth) You psycho.
啊，天啊！
Oh, my God!
那天晚上
我让他们去我爷爷家过夜
(Barry ) 'That night I set the guys up
at my grandparents' house.
我很久没去看他们了
'I haven't been there in a long time.
七岁那年我放火烧了他们的狗
'When I was seven years old
I set their dog on fire
此后再也没有被邀请过
'and wasn't invited back.
但我听说还不错
'But I hear it's still real nice.'
说真的，只准说“请”
I'm serious. "Please",
"Thank you", "This is delicious"
“谢谢”，   “很好吃”
are the only words
you're allowed to say.
老人都喜欢我，奶奶更爱我
What? I'm great with old people.
Grandmas love me.
等等，等等，   “曼尼露”？
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait. "Manilow"?
你巴里姓曼尼露？
你对
- Barry's last name is Manilow?
- Yeah.
你他叫巴里你曼尼露？
你对
- His name is Barry Manilow?
- Yeah.
你嗨！
你哎哟，天啊！
- (All) Hi!
- Oh, my goodness!
啊，瞧这些孩子
Oh, look at you boys.
杰克，他们来了！
Jack, they're here!
巴里的朋友来了，来打个招呼
Jack, Barry's friends are here.
Come and say hi.
他们来了
- (Dog groans )
- The boys are here.
你啊，嗨，小伙子
你嗨
- Oh, hey, fellas.
- Hi.
你嗨，你怎么样？
你等等，让我起来
- Hey, how's it going?
- Wait. Let me get up.
你我带你们看看
你啊，亲爱的！
- I'll give you guys the full tour.
- Oh, honey!
小心，你太不雅了！
Careful. Your boner!
你叫我怎么办？割了它？
Well, what do you want me to do,
cut it off?
这样吧，小伙子
(Groans ) I'll tell you what, fellas,
首先带你们看看睡觉的地方
we'll start by showin'
you where you're gonna sleep.
看看所谓的客房
(Chuckles ) I'll show you
what we call the guest room.
跟我来，孩子，客房…
Follow me, boys. The guest room...
对不起
Excuse me.
你见过这个孩子吗？
You remember this kid?
没有，肯定没有
No, sure don't.
该死的傻瓜
(Mutters ) Fuckin' airhead.
我再问一次，见过我儿子吗？
Let me ask you once more.
Have you seen my son?
我记起来了，是有几个人来过
Ow. Now that you mention it,
there were a few guys in.
放开我的手，我拿账单给你看
If you loosen my arm,
I could get their bill.
用另一只手拿
Use your other arm.
你几个人？
你就几个
- How many were there?
- A few.
四个！
- (Cracking)
- Aaah! Four!
其中一个还想买毒品
One of 'em was trying to score drugs.
他们打了两个电话去奥斯丁
他们可能去那儿了
Honey, look. They made two calls to
Austin, Texas. Maybe they went there.
早上2：18
(Door opens )
你抽烟？
(Grandpa ) Havin' a smoke?
对，对
Uh...yeah, yeah.
我也睡不着
(Groans ) I can't sleep, either.
该死的威格拉令我心跳加速
Goddam Viagra
gets my heart racing like a lab rat.
你没事儿吧？
(Chuckles ) Are you OK?
你你看起来闷闷不乐
你我没事儿
- You look kinda goofy.
- No. No, it's nothing.
你来，说出来吧
你好
- Come on, out with it.
- (Sniffs ) OK.
啊…两天前我差点儿死了
Well...I almost died two days ago.
你什么？
你我们的车子爆炸了
- What?
- Our car exploded.
我可能已经不在了
I could be dead right now.
之后我就问自己为什么？
And since that happened,
I find myself asking why.
你知道吗？就像…
You know? Like...
生命的目的是什么？
What is my reason for living?
你不把草烟递给我吗？
Are you gonna
pass that doobie, or what?
草烟？是，对不起
Doobie? Yeah. Yeah, sorry.
嗯，谢谢
Uh, thanks.
你知道你的问题是啥吗？
You know what your problem is?
只有脑袋没有雄心壮志
You're all brains.
Not enough cock and balls.
实际上，人们一直都这样说
Actually, uh, people have been
telling me that my whole life.
六年级时我为伊拉克形势担心
In the sixth grade I got so worried
about the situation in Iraq,
我要服成人剂量的镇静剂
that I was on
an adult dosage of Xanax.
八年级时每周三次见心理医生
And by eighth grade,
I was in therapy three times a week.
实情是，只有大麻才使我放松
And the truth is, weed is the
only thing that could balance me out.
你明白我的意思吗？像…
You know what I mean? Like...
你没事儿吧？
You OK?
喂，老人家
Hey, old man.
我真他妈的想吃东西
I got the fuckin' munchies real bad.
你呢？
(Dog) How 'bout you?
v芬妮，不要再伤心了
OK, Tiffany,
it's time to stop being so sad.
看你收到了这么多信
Look at all this mail you got!
看多少人在关心你
Look how many nice people
care about you.
还有乔希的包裹
You even got a package from Josh.
真的？
Really?
打开看看好吗？
Shall we open it
and see what he says?
好，来，打开看看
Yeah, come on, Tif. Let's open it.
是盘录像带
- (Laughs ) It's a tape.
- Oh.
那，放进去看看
Well, pop it in.
也许我应该一个人看
Maybe I should watch this on my own.
啊，来吧
Oh, come on.
这一定会使你开心
This'll definitely cheer you up.
你喜欢什么样的女孩子？
(Beth) 'What do you look for
in a girl? '
哦，让我想想，她要精明
'Well, let's see.
She should be smart...'
有趣，还…
- (Giggling)
- 'and, um, funny.
这也不错…不错
'That's good...that's good, too.'
还有呢？
(Beth) 'What else do you look for?'
她还要漂亮
'Um... She should be, uh, attractive.
啊…无上装
'And, um, topless.
她还要吻我
- 'Uh-huh.'
- 'And she should kiss me.'
你再见
你你们好好做人
(Josh) Bye-bye.
(Grandpa ) You boys be good now.
你再见
你我会代你向巴里问好
- Bye-bye.
- I'll tell Barry you said hello.
喂，杰克，叫那个婊子
弄点儿饼给我
Hey, Jack, have that bitch make me
some blueberry pancakes. Now.
星期一上午8：52奥斯丁大学
对不起，啊哟
Excuse me. Ahem.
网址是WWW…
www.episodetwo/spoilers...
好，瞧，我这里有人
(Sighs ) OK, look.
Some people are here
他们很无礼
and they are being very rude.
好，我再打给你
OK. Call you back.
对不起，我们需要你帮忙
I'm sorry, but we need your help.
你你认识v芬妮你安迪森吗？
你109号房间
- Do you know Tiffany Henderson?
- Room 109.
她的外祖父刚过世了
Well, her grandfather died,
她让我帮她取她的信件
and she asked me
to pick up her mail.
啊，真不幸，你有锁匙吗？
Oh, how sad. Do you have the key?
她没有带到丧礼那儿去
我希望你可以…
Well, she didn't bring it to the
funeral so I was hoping you could...
对不起，一定要有锁匙
Oh, I'm sorry,
but you need the key.
别担心，邮件在这儿很安全
Don't worry. Her mail will be here,
safe and sound.
不是担心，是她需要点儿东西
It's not like that, you see?
She needs something.
你这是紧急情况
你不要把事情搞大
- This is an emergency.
- Don't make a big deal out of it.
没有搞大，你得有钥匙
规矩就是规矩
Well, it's not a big deal, but
you need the key. Rules are rules.
没人让你犯错误，你就看别处
No one's asking you to do anything
wrong. Just, you know, look away.
去买个爱斯基莫馅饼
Go have an Eskimo pie.
你们必须离开
You guys are gonna have to leave.
拿不到邮件我们不走
We're not leaving without that mail.
听着，别让成龙揍扁你的脸
Listen to the man before you get
some Jackie Chan on your face.
你好，来吧
你现在就拿来，混蛋
- Come on, let's go.
- That means now, asshole.
上帝！
Jesus!
他打扁了我的鼻子，上帝！
I think he broke my nose. Oh, God!
来呀，小妞儿
Come on, Susie.
你你是摔角的？
你对，小妞儿，你想打吗？
- You're a wrestler?
- You bet, Mary. You wanna go?
你让我看看
你啊，上帝！
- Let me see it.
- Oh, God!
好
All right.
你谁是我的婊子？
你什么？！
- Who's my bitch?
- What?!
就这样，不，不！
(Receptionist) That's it. No, no, no!
好，各位，不准动！
OK, everyone, freeze!
这是胡椒喷雾
我们会毫不犹豫使用它的
This here is pepper spray,
and we will use it.
我坐在桌后，这些家伙袭击我
These guys jumped me.
I was just sitting behind my desk!
凯尔！
Kyle?
你爸爸？
你他是你爸爸？
- Dad?
- That's your dad?
别动，大家都别动！
Freeze now! Everybody freeze!
放下武器！
Put your weapon down now!
我儿子给绑架了！
My son was kidnapped!
啊…谁给绑架了？
Whoa, whoa... Who was kidnapped?
不是绑架，他们是我的同学
I wasn't kidnapped.
These are my friends from school.
你说什么？
What are you talkin' about?
我们一起来的
We all drove down here together.
什么？
What?
那告诉我车子怎么被炸了？
Then explain to me how
the frigging car got blown to hell!
你那…你瞧
你车子被偷了
- Well, see...
- It was stolen.
对，你说呀，凯尔
That's right. Tell him, Kyle.
一点儿不错
Uh-huh. Exactly.
被偷了？
Stolen?
那该死的信用卡呢？
What about the damned credit card?
一块儿都给偷了
It was inside,
and that was stolen, too.
废话！天方夜谈！
为什么不告诉我你的去处？
Bullcrap! This is ridiculous! Why
didn't you tell us where you were?
我知道你会发怒！你看？
Because I knew you'd get mad! See?
你我没发怒，马上跟我来
你乔希？
- I'm not mad! You're going with me.
- Josh?
你v芬妮！
你这…这怎么了？
- Tiffany!
- What the... What's going on?
你没什么
你嘿，伙计，她真撩人！
- Nothing.
- Damn, dude, she is hot!
我女友呼我，放他们走好吧？
My girlfriend's pagin' me.
Can we let them go?
你好主意
你谁也别动！
- Good idea.
- No one is going anywhere!
你他跟我走
你放开我！
- He's comin' with me.
- Get off of me!
我跟他们一块儿回去
I'm going back with these guys.
你闭嘴，别反嘴
Shut your mouth and don't talk back.
你为什么不闭嘴？
Why don't YOU shut up?
你刚才对我说什么？
What the hell did you just say to me?
我说，你闭嘴
I said, you shut up.
你总是让我维护自己的权益
You've always told me
to stand up for myself.
我现在做了，别管我，笨蛋！
Well, now I am.
Leave me alone, you jerk!
你这个无意…
You ungrateful...
你什么…
你这边儿走
- What...
- Go this way.
走开！走开！
Go away! Go away!
怎么回事儿？你来干什么？
What was that all about? I mean,
Josh, what are you doing here?
我就是想你，没别的
I just missed you. That's all.
我也想你
但这么远开车来有点发疯
I missed you, too, but it's crazy
for you to drive all the way here.
什么？我以为你会高兴呢
What?
I thought you'd be glad to see me.
当然高兴，但你要上学念书
I am. But Josh, you have your
entire life to live up at school.
这不利于健康，此外…
This isn't healthy. Besides...
这个周我意识到了一些事情
I realised a few things
this past week.
是吗？什么事情？
You did? Like what?
比如，我们在念大学
Like, we're in college.
去玩儿、去认识人的机会
The window of opportunity to go out
and have fun and meet new people
变得越来越小
is getting smaller by the day.
你是吗？
你别这样，乔希
- It is?
- Come on, Josh.
我们一直在一起
We've been together forever.
我是说…
你几乎.上是我唯一的男友
I mean...you're pretty much
the only guy I've ever been with.
“几乎.唯一的”是什么意思？
What do you mean,
"pretty much the only guy"?
我十四岁那年，你去露营了
那是多年以前的事
Well, I was 14, and you were away
at camp, but that was years ago.
此外，我们处于不同的地区
Besides,
we're in different area codes.
我也想过不少我们的关系
I've been thinking a lot
about us, too.
我来的真正原因是…
The real reason I drove down...
等等
Hold that thought.
喂？
Hello?
对，他在这儿
Yeah, he's right here.
你是谁？
Who is this?
等等
Hold on.
找你的，是贝思
It's for you. It's Beth.
贝思是谁？
Who's Beth?
贝思，你怎么了？
Beth? What are you doing?
我不知道我们怎么了
但我得告诉你一件事情
I'm not sure what's going on between
us but I need to tell you something.
我很高兴你来电话
我也有事要告诉你
I'm actually glad you called,
cos I wanted to tell you something.
好，你先讲
OK, you first.
现在不太方便
I can't really talk right now,
我回去后一定好好解释
but I'll explain everything
when I get back.
好吧？真的，我保证
'OK? Really. I promise.'
我要挂了，好吗？
Uh, I-I gotta get going, OK?
你等等，你不想听我的吗？
你对，抱歉
- Wait! Do you want to hear mine?
- Right. Sorry.
是好消息？
Is it good?
恐怕不是，雅各布骗了你
Not really. Jacob lied to you.
期中考试你不能延期
There's no extension
on your mid-term.
什么？
What?
他耍你，你回不来就过不了
'He tried to trick you. If you
don't get back you're gonna fail.'
混蛋！
Shit!
她应该精明，有趣
'She should be smart and funny.'
你我来电话你高兴吗？
你高兴，谢谢
- 'Aren't you glad I called?'
- Yes. Thank you.
我一回去就给你打电话，再见
I'll call you as soon
as I get back, OK? Bye.
这是给我的？
- Is this for me?
- Hmm?
啊，天啊，不！你别…
Oh, God, no, no, no! You don't...
这是什么？
What the hell is this?
我上电视了，再倒带看看
'I can see myself on TV,
I think it must be rewound.'
是巴里
It's Barry.
嗨，看…
'Hey, look...
看，我看到我的屁股了
'Look at that. I can see my bum.
(Laughs )'
你为什么给我这个？
Why would you send this to me?
等等你你们分手了
拥抱后你就离开了？
So wait - you guys broke up,
then you hugged and then you left?
对，大致是这样
Yeah, pretty much.
输家！分手前一定要再来一次
Loser! Always have sex with the girl
one last time before you break up.
谁都会这样！
Everyone knows that!
不能那样，我认识她很久
她是我最好的朋友
It's not like that. I've known her
my whole life. She's my best friend.
那，我们现在干什么？
So, what do we do now?
你想抽两口吗？
你不抽
- Wanna smoke some drugs?
- I don't think so.
再过46小时就要考试了
我必须回去
My mid-term starts in exactly
46 hours so I got to get back.
虽然我不会通过，但…
Although I'm gonna fail anyway,
so it doesn't matter but...
你考什么试？
你古代哲学
- Which class was it?
- Ancient Philosophy.
我能在46小时之内教会你
I can teach you ancient philosophy
in 46 hours.
你能？
You can?
我能在46小时内教会猴子
I can teach a monkey in 46 hours.
关键是让你有兴趣
You just got to find a way
to relate to the material.
就像…你喜欢职业摔角吗？
Like, OK...
You like pro wrestling, don't you?
你谁不喜欢？
你好
- Who doesn't?
- OK.
苏格拉底就是哲学上的温森
Socrates was like
the Vince McMahon of philosophy.
他发起了哲学
He started it all.
两天之后艾菲嘉大学
晚了57分钟
啊，二十人皇家大战是什么？
Oh, what was the 20-Man Battle Royal?
参与解释预言，亚里士多德
Participation explains predication.
Aristotle.
对
Right.
你懂这个！你没事儿
You know this! You'll be fine.
站住，呆那儿！别动！
Freeze, right there! Don't move!
这是哲学课吗？
Is this philosophy?
有什么消息，打电话给我
If you hear anything, give me a call.
炸弹威胁是重罪，我的名片
A bomb threat is serious.
Take my card.
好
- OK.
- (Sirens wailing)
好，我们走吧
(Cop ) OK, let's move it.
炸弹威胁是怎么回事儿？
What's goin' on
with this bomb threat?
谎报，各位，大家回去
False alarm, people.
Everyone back inside.
我们要考试了，对
We're gonna do this thing.
That's right.
你乔希
你贝思！
- Josh.
- Beth!
嗨…谢谢你的电话
Hey, um...thanks for calling.
这个星期真离奇
Uh, it's been a really weird week.
你考得怎么样？
So, how'd you do?
实际上，很不错
On the exam? Pretty good, actually.
你真的？
你真的
- You did?
- Yeah.
你感到奇怪吗？
Were you surprised?
你考试来晚了
You weren't back
in time for the exam,
于是我打电话说有炸弹…
so I, uh, called in a bomb threat.
是你打的？
You did that?
你发疯了
(Laughs ) That's insane.
我不能让雅各布赶你出校
I wasn't gonna let Jacob
get you kicked out.
此外，下学期我会需要你
Besides, I might need you
around next semester.
我没做错，对吧？
So I did good, right?
做错？
Good?
这是别人为我做的最棒的事
That's the coolest thing
anyone's ever done for me.
妈妈？
Mom?
对不起
(Panting) I'm so sorry.
妈妈？
Mom?
故事使我情不自禁
I got carried away
with the story there.
不管怎样，乔希得到了B+
So, anyway,
Josh got a B+ on his mid-term.
继续上学
He got to stay in college.
他现在仍和贝思在一起
'And he and Beth are still together.
他们仍喜欢拍…家庭录像
'They're still really into
making their...home movies.
实际上，他们有70小时的毛片
'In fact, they have about 70 hours
of unedited amateur video.'
很来劲
It's pretty wild.
我看了，因为我买了一些
I know, because I bought some of it.
那个雅各布呢？
That guy Jacob?
他离开学校了
到爱何华州当邪教领袖
'He left school. He went on to become
the leader of some cult in Iowa.
他组织了一次集体自杀
'He tried organising a mass suicide.
他率先喝了毒药
'Only problem is,
he drank the Kool-Aid first
信众们却改变了主意
'and, well, everyone else
just kind of changed their minds.'
真可惜
Too bad.
至于鲁宾…记得他吗？
As for Rubin... Remember Rubin?
记得他说他注定要做大事？
Remember how he claimed that
he was destined for great things?
我感到人类会需要我
(Rubin ) The people of Earth need me.
他说对了
Well, he was right.
他杂交出新的大麻品种
Rubin used cross-pollination
to develop a strain of marijuana
不但威力无比…
that is not only remarkably potent...
而且什么毒品测试都测不出
but completely undetectable
by any drug tests.
啊，上帝
Oh, my God.
他被评为“时代”年度伟人
'He was named
High Times' man of the year.'
至于EL
尽管他有不稳定的性理论
As for EL, despite his
swinging philosophy on sexuality,
也有了固定的女朋友
he got serious with some girl he met.
你要我用两个手指吗？
And you want me to use two fingers?
我想她是医学院预科生
'I believe she was pre-med.'
我说用两个？不如用三个
Did I say two? Better make it three.
还有凯尔
Then there's Kyle.
他和他爸爸冰释前嫌
'Kyle and his father
reconciled their differences.'
嗨，爸爸，圣诞快乐
Hi, Dad. Merry Christmas.
他把他的女友带回家
'He brought his girlfriend home.'
达朗，这是我爸爸厄尔
Rhonda, this is my father, Earl.
爸爸，这是朗达
Dad, this is Rhonda.
圣诞快乐，爸爸
Merry Christmas, Dad.
过来
Come here.
校园参观到此结束
That's the end of the tour.
我十分希望大家来读本大学
I hope you strongly consider becoming
part of the Ithaca tradition,
在新世纪到来的时刻
as we lead future generations
of young people
领导你们继往开来
forward into the new century.
谢谢大家，你们是好听众
Thanks a lot. You were great. Thanks.
你谢谢你
你不用，我喜欢讲
- Thank you so much.
- No, it was fun.
秋天开学见，谢谢
I'll see you in the fall.
Thank you. Thank you.
你啊，谢谢
你我只想说声谢谢
- OK. Thank you.
- I'd like to say thank you.
我是说…这故事
I mean, uh, that was...
太棒了
really great.
谢谢
Thank you.
妈妈？
(Boy ) Mom?
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢，妈妈
Thank you, Mommy.
我在为你妈妈做人工呼吸
I'm pumping your mommy.